{level: "B2",
author: "British Council",
test: {
		numquestions: 10,
		questions: [{   qnumber: 1,
						numanswers: 3,
						question: "Many famous and successful teenagers have...",
						answer1: "used new technology",
						answer2: "worked from an early age",
						answer3: "been inspired by YouTube videos",
						correctanswer: 1},
						{qnumber: 2,
						numanswers: 3,
						question: "Justin Bieber started off...",
						answer1: "singing with R&B star Usher",
						answer2: "ending videos to talent scouts",
						answer3: "posting videos on YouTube",
						correctanswer: 3},
						{qnumber: 3,
						numanswers: 3,
						question: "Some people say Justin Bieber is the most influential person in the world because...",
						answer1: "he has had so many number one songs",
						answer2: "he has so many followers on Twitter",
						answer3: "he is friends with Barack Obama",
						correctanswer: 2},
						{qnumber: 4,
						numanswers: 3,
						question: "A negative consequence of fame for Justin Bieber is...",
						answer1: "he has very little privacy",
						answer2: "people get bored of hearing about him",
						answer3: "people criticise his appearance",
						correctanswer: 1},
						{qnumber: 5,
						numanswers: 3,
						question: "Tavi Gevinson started a fashion blog...",
						answer1: "when she was 11 years old",
						answer2: "when she was in 11th grade in high school",
						answer3: "in 2011",
						correctanswer: 1},
                        {qnumber: 6,
						numanswers: 3,
						question: "'Rookie' means...",
						answer1: "a beginner",
						answer2: "a fan",
						answer3: "someone who is bad at something",
						correctanswer: 1},
						{qnumber: 7,
						numanswers: 3,
						question: "Style Rookie...",
						answer1: "allowed readers to post pictures of themselves",
						answer2: "soon had a lot of readers",
						answer3: "was noticed by Kark Lagerfeld",
						correctanswer: 2},
                        {qnumber: 8,
						numanswers: 3,
						question: "When some people didn't believe her age, Tavi...",
						answer1: "was sad and angry at first",
						answer2: "decided to attack them in return",
						answer3: "completely ignored them and continued working",
						correctanswer: 1},
						{qnumber: 9,
						numanswers: 3,
						question: "Tavi employs...",
						answer1: "only teenagers",
						answer2: "writers and photograpers of all ages",
						answer3: "a very small group of people",
						correctanswer: 2},
                        {qnumber: 10,
						numanswers: 3,
						question: "Louise...",
						answer1: "thinks it's difficult for Tavi to have a normal life",
						answer2: "there's more pressure when you are a writer",
						answer3: "there's more pressure when you are a performer",
						correctanswer: 3}
					]
	}
}
